Yeah I mean you
know I think how
we think about that
is you as we've
better and models there's
been a kind of
relationship not only between
how much compute you
put into the and
how cognitively it is
but between how cognitively
it is and how
much revenue it's able
to So our revenue
has 10x in the
last three years from
zero to 100 million
in 2023 100 million
to a billion in
2024 and 1 billion
to 10 billion in
2025 And so those
revenue numbers you I
don't know if that
curve will literally continue
It would be crazy
if it did But
those numbers are starting
to get not too
far from you the
scale of the companies
in the world So
there's always uncertainty You
we're trying to bootstrap
this from nothing It's
a crazy thing But
I have confidence that
if we're able to
the best models in
the things that we
focus on then I
think things will go
well And you I
will generally say you
I think it's been
a good year for
both Google and Entropic
And I think the
thing we actually have
in is that they're
both kind of companies
that are you or
the research part of
the company that are
kind of by who
focus on the who
focus on important problems
in the right who
have these kind hard
scientific problems as a
North Star